White, W. I. Papers 5905
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
W. I. White Papers
1906-1943
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
White, W. I.
5905
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Papers.
5731972
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 16, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Stein, Leon, 1912-; Thomas, W. I.
5731972
- Series 1: Chronological Order (Box 1)
  - January 1906 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - March 1906 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - August 1906 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - May 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - June 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - July-December 1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - January-March 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - December 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - January-December 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - January-September 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Discarded Bintel Brief (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series II: Subject Files (Box 2)
  - Personal (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Personal (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The American Experience (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Asking Definitions (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Asking Definitions (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bitter Heart (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Nave Humorous (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Exploratory (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Testimony (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Testimony (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Asking Editor to Reprove (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Trivial (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Outsider Writes (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Kin (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Family and Marriage as Ritual (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Family and Marriage as Ritual (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Desertion, Divorce, and Reunion (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Compulsions (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Overt Emotion (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fear of Scandal (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Inability to Live Alone (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Boarder (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bundle (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Shall I tell? (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Family and Community Solidarity (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Instances where help is given (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Gossip (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Relatives (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Relatives (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Children of Dead Relatives (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Children of Dead Relatives (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Children of Dead Relatives (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Savior of Fallen Girls (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Conscience, Confession, Apology (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Solidarity (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Solidarity (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Unsocial March 1943 WISH (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Scope and Contents
    March 1943
  - Social Devotion (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Social Devotion (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Shall I go? (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Shall They Invite Him (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Series II: Subject Files (continued) (Box 3)
  - Disorganization (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Disharmony of Generations (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Disharmony of Generations (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Disharmony of Generations (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Disharmony of Generations (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Disharmony of Generations (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Rejection and Ritual (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Rejection (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Evil Tongues (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Missionary (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Betrayals in Marriage (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Betrayals in Courtship (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Alleged Insanity (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mobility in Marriage (Divorce) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mixed Marriage (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mixed Marriage (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Mixed Marriage (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Seduction and Ruin (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Marital Difficulties (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Marital Difficulties (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Marital Difficulties (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Marital Difficulties (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Marital Difficulties (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Family Mad (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Vent (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Silent (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Stony Heart (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jealous Mix (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Karger (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Gambler (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - The All Right Nilc (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The White Slaver (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - The Boarder as an Organizing Force (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Alcoholism (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Business Opportunism (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Business Opportunism (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Mobility as a form of adjustment (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Mobility as a form of adjustment (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Learning as Distinction (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Ritual (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Stubborn (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Nave (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bizarre (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Bizarre (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Cynical (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Fanatic (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Depressed (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Inquisitiveness in General (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Series III: Names (Stories by Person) - Miscellaneous Files (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Files (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Antonoff, Rosa (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Barinowsky, Jacob (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Borenstein, Jacob (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Eisenman, Bunim (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Friedman, Leibke (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hornsohn, David (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Kahn, Liza (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Katzin, Daniel (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kossovsky, Abraham (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kossovsky, Minnie (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Landsberg, Anna (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Levin, Meyer (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Mandel, Bessie (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Margolis, Esther (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Menes, Adela (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Newman, Simcha (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ohrbach, John (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Olishevsky, Henry (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Perlman, Anna (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Perlstein, Eta (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Preedland, J. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Sandberg, Eta (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Schlesel, Isador (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Silver, Judith (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Silver, Sam (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Sonnenshein, Abraham (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Spenser, Sarah (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Steinman, Sarah (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Weiser, Gustav (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 31)